simplytest.me 2015-09-06

# Privacy policy | simplytest.me

We are keenly aware of the trust users place in us and our responsibility to protect the privacy of user information. As part of this responsibility, we make public what information we collect when someone uses our products and services, why we collect it and how we use it to improve user experience.

## Information we collect to provide you with the services includes:

  * Device information: We may collect device-specific information (such as your hardware model, operating system version, unique device identifiers, and mobile network information including phone number).
  * Log information: When you use our services or view content provided by simplytest.me, we may automatically collect and store certain information in server logs. This may include: details of how you used our service; Internet protocol address; device event information such as crashes, system activity, hardware settings, browser type, standard HTTP request headers, including but not limited to user agent, referral URL, language preference, date and time; and cookies that may uniquely identify your browser or your simplytest.me Account.
  * Cookies and Local Storage: We use various technologies to collect and store information when you visit the website, and this may include sending one or more cookies or randomly generated identifiers to your device. A cookie is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. Cookies may store user preferences and other information. The "help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. However, some of simplytest.me's website features or services may not function properly without cookies. We may also collect and store information using mechanisms such as browser web storage (including HTML5) and application data caches.

## How we use information we collect

     We use the information we collect from all of our services to provide, maintain, protect and improve them, to develop new services, and to protect simplytest.me and our users. 

When you contact simplytest.me, we may keep a record of your communication to help solve any issues you might be facing. We may use your email address to inform you about our services where you have agreed to this. We may also send you administrative messages.

simplytest.me processes personal information on servers in many countries around the world. We may process, transfer and/or store your personal information on a server located outside the country where you live. When we do so simplytest.me will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  

## Information we share

     We provide personal information to our affiliates or other trusted businesses or persons to process it for us, based on our instructions and in compliance with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.  
For legal reasons. We will share personal information with companies, organisations or individuals outside of simplytest.me if we believe that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to:  
meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request.  
enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations.  
detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues.  
protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of simplytest.me, our users or the public as required or permitted by law.  
We may share aggregated, anonymised information publicly and with our partners. For example, we may share information publicly to show statistical trends about the general use of our services.  

## Information security

     Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.  

## Your Rights

     We will let you know if we plan to process your personal data for marketing purposes when we collect it. You can change your mind at any time by contacting us through the contact form. 

You also have the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Data Protection Acts 1988 and 2003. Any access request may be subject to a statutory fee to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.  

## Application

     Our website may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partners and members of the simplytest.me website. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.  

## Enforcement

     We will regularly review our compliance with our Privacy Policy. When we receive formal written complaints, we will contact the person who made the complaint to follow up. We will work with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that we cannot resolve with our users directly.  

## Changes

     Any changes we may make to our Privacy Policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail.  

## Contact Us

     If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us through the contact form.  

Privacy Policy Effective Date: 18 September 2012
